You're the one with the problem
You're just afraid Daniel's frogs are better than yours
I know
It's hard to admit you were wrong
But it's fine
When Walter gives the multi-million order
to Daniel
you'll be on your knees admitting it
Business isn't about who works the hardest
It's about having good judgment
And putting people to good use
In this regard
you're far behind
Words can't save a doomed man
Uncle
There's something wrong with this bucket of frogs
Don't eat them
They look fine to me
Monster
Lewes
The four months are up
I'm here for the goods
After you, Mr. Walter
Wait, Mr. Walter
You are
I'm Daniel from the farm across the way
Listen to me
Lewes's frogs have problems
All his workers ran away
The frogs have been starving for days
He can't deliver at all
Exactly
All of Lewes's workers ran off
I heard the frogs all starved to death
I heard that too
He mistreated his workers and drove them away
No one is working for him
Mr. Walter
I used to work for Lewes
When I left
his frogs were thin and small
They were on the verge of dying
Lewes
Frogs that don't meet the standard
I won't accept
According to the contract
you must pay me a thirty million penalty
Walter
My frogs are fine
You'll see if you take a look yourself
Stop wasting Walter's time
Walter
His frogs
haven't been cared for in a month
Even if they aren't all dead
they definitely won't meet your standard
How about
you look at my frogs first
Big and fat
And the price
is thirty percent lower than Lewes's
Well
Lewes
Look
Business is about comparing options
I understand
Go check out his place first
After you look around
it won't be too late to decide
Let's go
After you